<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Turner</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to my webpage where you will see some of my high tech computational skills. I am currently a Junior at the University of Texas and am working towards earning a degree in biochemistry. With the plethora of opportunities available at UT,I have filled my past three years here with research, volunteering, and personal growth.  I currently work at a pediatric physical therapy office where I assist the lead physical therapists with treating children who either have some sort of physical injury or functional disability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interesting Stuff</title>
      <link>/blog/interesting-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/interesting-stuff/</guid>
      <description>SDS 348 has been a very informative joyride, I don’t think I’ve ever been so frsutrated yet intrigued at the same time. After months of the glorious Rstudio, we got to learn a bit about the great Python.
For example we learned different type of loops, such as the following while loop:
mine=[1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9] i=0 while i &amp;lt; len(mine): i2=2**mine[i] print(i2) i+=1 ## 2 ## 4 ## 8 ## 16 ## 32 ## 64 ## 128 ## 256 ## 512 Additionally, I found regex (esp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Willingness to Pay for the Preservation of the Kakadu National Park</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>I chose the Willingness to Pay for the Preservation of the Kakadu National Park dataset which is from a a survey collected in australia about locals and their opinions on forest conservation. The varibales I chose to analyze include basic demographic information such as age,income,and years of schooling. I was interested in how these demographics would effect/relate to the response varibales such as wildlife (believe it’s important to have places where wildlife is preserved),moreparks (there should be more national parks created from state forests),aboriginal(in deciding how to use areas such as Kakadu national park, their importance to the local aboriginal people should be a major factor) and jobs (jobs are the most important thing in deciding how to use our natural resources).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Sunspots on Bee Colonies</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>I chose to analyze the effects of the number of sunspots on the number of bee colonies in the United states. To do so, I combined the honey production and sunspot data sets. The sunspot dataset contains the monthly mean relative number of sunspots for each month from the years of 1749 to 2013. The honey production dataset contains the number of colonies, yield per colony, production of honey and additional related variables for the 50 united states from 1998 to 2012</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>